

SUMMARY

I am UX/UI Designer with a passion for applying my creativity and attention to detail in the design of user-centered products, and offering them the best possible user experience. I come from a background in Graphic Design and Photography and am a recent graduate of Ironhack Miami's UX/UI Design intensive bootcamp.

CONTACT



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Design Tools		Design Skills	
Figma	Maze	Lean UX	User Research
Sketch	Flinto	Wireframes	Usability Testing
Adobe XD	Marvel	Visual Design	Market Research
Illustrator	InVision	Interaction Design	Agile Methodology
Photoshop	Webflow	Rapid Prototyping	Information Architecture

WORK HISTORY

From May 2017 to October 2020

Graphic Designer

My Cosmetic Surgery INC - Miami FL

- Participation in the design and preparation of advertising campaigns for thousands of clients and more than a million dollars in profits.
- Realization of projects through coordination with external agencies, art services, printers, etc.
- Management of various projects within the design and budget specifications.

From January 2014 to May 2017

Photographer and Video Editor

Self Employed - Miami FL

- Take pictures of individuals, families, and parties (weddings, birthdays, and corporate events with between 30 and 100 guests).
- Determine, configured, and adjusted subject position, accessories, lighting equipment, and camera angles.
- Capture and produced clear and sharp photos, operating and maintaining a variety of cameras to take them correctly.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

From October 2020 to December 2020

UX/UI Design - 400 Plus Hours

Ironhack - Miami FL

From January 2018 to May 2020

Associate of Arts - AA

Miami Dade College - Miami FL